// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Who invented C++?",
      answer: "Bjarne Stroustrup",
      options: [
        "Dennis Ritchie",
        " Ken Thompson",
        " Brian Kernighan",
        "Bjarne Stroustrup"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: " C++ is ______________",
      answer: "both procedural and object oriented programming language",
      options: [
        "object-oriented programming",
        "procedural programming language",
        "both procedural and object oriented programming language",
        " functional programming language"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "Which of the following is the correct syntax of including a user defined header files in C++?",
      answer: "#include “userdefined”",
      options: [
        "#include [userdefined]",
        "#include “userdefined”",
        " #include <userdefined.h>",
        " #include <userdefined>"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Which of the following is used for comments in C++?",
      answer: " both // comment or /* comment */",
      options: [
        "/* comment */",
        " // comment */",
        "// comment",
        " both // comment or /* comment */"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: " Which of the following user-defined header file extension used in c++?",
      answer: "h",
      options: [
        " hg",
        "cpp",
        " h",
        "hf"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which of the following is a correct identifier in C++?",
      answer: "VAR_1234",
      options: [
        "VAR_1234",
        " $var_name",
        "7VARNAME",
        "7var_name"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Which of the following is not a type of Constructor in C++?",
      answer: "Friend constructor",
      options: [
        "Default constructor",
        "Parameterized constructor",
        " Copy constructor",
        "Friend constructor"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: " Which of the following approach is used by C++?",
      answer: "Bottom-up",
      options: [
        "Left-right",
        "Right-left",
        "Bottom-up",
        "Top-down"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "What is virtual inheritance in C++?",
      answer: "C++ technique to avoid multiple copies of the base class into children/derived class",
      options: [
        "C++ technique to enhance multiple inheritance",
        "C++ technique to ensure that a private member of the base class can be accessed somehow",
        "C++ technique to avoid multiple inheritances of classes",
        " C++ technique to avoid multiple copies of the base class into children/derived class"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: " Which of the following is correct about this pointer in C++?",
      answer: "this pointer is passed as a hidden argument in all non-static functions of a class",
      options: [
        "this pointer is passed as a hidden argument in all static variables of a class",
        "this pointer is passed as a hidden argument in all the functions of a class",
        "this pointer is passed as a hidden argument in all non-static functions of a class",
        " this pointer is passed as a hidden argument in all static functions of a class"
      ]
    },
  ];